(mysterious laughter)
- Welcome to the fantasy.
(clown laughs)
(music begins)
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Yeah, Yeah, Yeah ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Oh-Oh ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Sho do do do do do do do ♪
♪ Sho do do do do do do yeah ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Sho do do do do do do do ♪
♪ Sho do do do do do do yeah ♪
♪ Oh baby ♪
♪ Oh, when you walk by every night ♪
♪ Talking sweet and looking fine ♪
♪ I get kind of hectic inside ♪
♪ Mm, baby, I'm so into you ♪
♪ Darling, if you only knew ♪
♪ All the things that
flow through my mind ♪
♪ But it's just a sweet,
sweet fantasy, baby ♪
♪ When I close my eyes,
you come and take me ♪
♪ On and on and on, it's
so deep in my daydreams ♪
♪ But it's just a sweet,
sweet fantasy, baby ♪
♪ Fantasy ♪
♪ Sho do do do do do do do ♪
♪ Sho do do do do do do yeah ♪
♪ And I want you, oh, oh, baby ♪
♪ Sho do do do do do do do ♪
♪ Sho do do do do do do so ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Images of rapture ♪
♪ Creep into me slowly ♪
♪ As you're going to my head ♪
♪ And my heart beats faster ♪
♪ When you take me over ♪
♪ Time and time and time again ♪
♪ But it's just a sweet,
sweet fantasy, baby ♪
♪ When I close my eyes,
you come and take me ♪
♪ On and on and on, it's
so deep in my daydreams ♪
♪ But it's just a sweet,
sweet fantasy, baby ♪
♪ Fantasy ♪
♪ Sho do do do do do do do ♪
♪ Sho do do do do do do yeah ♪
♪ Sho do do do do do do do so ♪
♪ Oh, I want you so bad ♪
♪ Sho do do do do do do yeah ♪
♪ Oh, oh, it's just a sweet ♪
♪ Sweet, sweet, fantasy, baby ♪
♪ When I close my eyes
you come and take me ♪
♪ On and on and on, it's
so deep in my daydreams ♪
♪ But it's just a sweet,
sweet fantasy, baby ♪
♪ Fantasy ♪
♪ I'm in heaven ♪
♪ With my boyfriend,
my laughing boyfriend ♪
♪ There's no beginning
and there is no end ♪
♪ Feels like I'm dreaming,
but I'm not sleeping ♪
♪ Oh, it's just a sweet,
sweet fantasy, baby ♪
♪ When I close my eyes,
you come and take me ♪
♪ On and on and on, it's
so deep in my daydreams ♪
♪ But it's just a sweet,
sweet fantasy, baby ♪
♪ Sweet, sweet fantasy, baby ♪
♪ When I close my eyes,
you come and take me ♪
♪ On and on and on, it's
so deep in my daydreams ♪
♪ But it's just a sweet,
sweet fantasy, baby ♪
♪ Sweet, sweet fantasy, baby ♪
♪ Come and take me ♪
♪ Sweet, sweet, baby ♪
♪ Sweet baby ♪
♪ Sho do do do do do do do ♪
♪ Sweet, sweet baby, Sweet baby ♪
♪ Fantasy ♪
♪ Sho do do do do do do do ♪
(music fades out)